<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Quotes about reading for index page -->
<quotes>
	<quote>
		<text>No two persons ever read the same book.</text>
		<author>Edmund Wilson</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>A book is a dream that you hold in your hand.</text>
		<author>Neil Gaiman</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Whenever you read a good book, somewhere in the world a door opens to allow in more light.</text>
		<author>Vera Nazarian</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>If we encounter a man of rare intellect, we should ask him what books he reads.</text>
		<author>Ralph Waldo Emerson</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>There comes a time when you have to choose between turning the page and closing the book.</text>
		<author>Josh Jameson</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>I would never read a book if it were possible for me to talk half an hour with the man who wrote it.</text>
		<author>Woodrow Wilson</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Always read something that will make you look good if you die in the middle of it.</text>
		<author>P.J. O'Rourke</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Anyone who says they have only one life to live must not know how to read a book.</text>
		<author>Author Unknown</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>I think of life as a good book. The further you get into it, the more it begins to make sense.</text>
		<author>Harold Kushner</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>If you only read the books that everyone else is reading, you can only think what everyone else is thinking.
		</text>
		<author>Haruki Murakami</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>There are many little ways to enlarge your child's world. Love of books is the best of all.</text>
		<author>Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Any book that helps a child to form a habit of reading, to make reading one of his deep and continuing needs, is
			good for him.
		</text>
		<author>Maya Angelou</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>The book you don't read won't help.</text>
		<author>Jim Rohn</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Great books help you understand, and they help you feel understood.</text>
		<author>John Green</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>A good novel tells us the truth about its hero; but a bad novel tells us the truth about its author.</text>
		<author>Gilbert K. Chesterton</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>There is a great deal of difference between an eager man who wants to read a book and the tired man who wants a
			book to read.
		</text>
		<author>Gilbert K. Chesterton</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>A book is a version of the world. If you do not like it, ignore it or offer your own version in return.</text>
		<author>Salman Rushdie</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>In a good book the best is between the lines.</text>
		<author>Swedish Proverb</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Are we not like two volumes of one book?</text>
		<author>Marceline Desbordes-Valmore</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Keep reading books, but remember that a book is only a book, and you should learn to think for yourself.</text>
		<author>Maxim Gorky</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>It is what you read when you don't have to that determines what you will be when you can't help it.</text>
		<author>Oscar Wilde</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>There are perhaps no days of our childhood we lived so fully as those we spent with a favorite book.</text>
		<author>Marcel Proust</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>The books that the world calls immoral are books that show the world its own shame.</text>
		<author>Oscar Wilde</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Beware of the person of one book.</text>
		<author>Thomas Aquinas</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>A book is the only place in which you can examine a fragile thought without breaking it.</text>
		<author>Edward P. Morgan</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>If one cannot enjoy reading a book over and over again, there is no use in reading it at all.</text>
		<author>Oscar Wilde</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>The only important thing in a book is the meaning that it has for you.</text>
		<author>W. Somerset Maugham</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Read the best books first, or you may not have a chance to read them at all.</text>
		<author>Henry David Thoreau</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Reading a book is like re-writing it for yourself.</text>
		<author>Angela Carter</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>There's nothing wrong with reading a book you love over and over.</text>
		<author>Gail Carson Levine</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>It is a good rule after reading a new book, never to allow yourself another new one till you have read an old
			one in between.
		</text>
		<author>C.S. Lewis</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Make it a rule never to give a child a book you would not read yourself.</text>
		<author>George Bernard Shaw</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Books serve to show a man that those original thoughts of his aren't very new after all.</text>
		<author>Abraham Lincoln</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>I can't imagine a man really enjoying a book and reading it only once.</text>
		<author>C.S. Lewis</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Where is human nature so weak as in the bookstore?</text>
		<author>Henry Ward Beecher</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>A great book should leave you with many experiences, and slightly exhausted at the end. You live several lives
			while reading.
		</text>
		<author>William Styron</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>One always has a better book in one's mind than one can manage to get onto paper.</text>
		<author>Michael Cunningham</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>I divide all readers into two classes; those who read to remember and those who read to forget.</text>
		<author>William Lyon Phelps</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>In old days books were written by men of letters and read by the public. Nowadays books are written by the
			public and read by nobody.
		</text>
		<author>Oscar Wilde</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>There are worse crimes than burning books. One of them is not reading them.</text>
		<author>Joseph Brodsky</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>What you don't know would make a great book.</text>
		<author>Sydney Smith</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>You know you've read a good book when you turn the last page and feel a little as if you have lost a friend.
		</text>
		<author>Paul Sweeney</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>I cannot sleep unless I am surrounded by books.</text>
		<author>Jorge Luis Borges</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Some books leave us free and some books make us free.</text>
		<author>Ralph Waldo Emerson</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>A good book has no ending.</text>
		<author>R.D. Cumming</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>That is a good book which is opened with expectation and closed with profit.</text>
		<author>Amos Bronson Alcott</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Once you learn to read, you will be forever free.</text>
		<author>Frederick Douglas</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>Books are like mirrors: if a fool looks in, you cannot expect a genius to look out.</text>
		<author>J.K. Rowling</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>A book is a device to ignite the imagination.</text>
		<author>Alan Bennett</author>
	</quote>

	<quote>
		<text>It's not just the books under fire now that worry me. It is the books that will never be written. The books that
			will never be read.
		</text>
		<author>Judy Blume</author>
	</quote>
</quotes>